Last night, President Donald Trump delivered a primetime address, so let's talk about what he said and why it's important to pay attention to.
Much of the address was centered around the continued conspiracy that the 2020 election was rigged and an urge for Congress to pass the Save America Act.
This is extremely important to keep an eye on. The 2020 election is not being brought up as a pointless beating of a dead horse.
This is a political strategy and it's being used to attempt to shift the scale in upcoming elections.
First and foremost, claims that the 2020 election was stolen or rigged are straight-up lies, and last night's address was continued spread of misinformation.
Countless investigations, audits, recounts, and over 50 court proceedings invested the
2020 election, and all of them came back with the same consensus, that the 2020 election
was legit.
And Trump and his buddies know this, but they also know that by continuing to push this
rigged election story into the heads of the American people, they are weakening the systems
that uphold democracy and putting that power right back into their hands.
Election denialism is a strategy that has been used throughout history by leaders as
an attempt to abuse power, and this is threatening to democracy.
Additionally, last night Donald Trump's push for Congress to pass the Save America Act,
which is a voter suppression bill, shows that if this administration has the chance to do
anything to make voting less inclusive, they will take it.
So pay attention, stay aware, and if you can do anything to get involved or make your voice
heard, do it.
That's all she wrote.
Bye guys!